Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. records 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives Box 90772 Durham, North Carolina, 27708-0772 USA Phone: 919-684-6402 Fax: 919-684-5459 Email: adfarchives@americandancefestival.org
Charles Reinhart Management, Inc.
97.25 linear feet Extent: 972,500 Items
Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. (CRMI) was involved in dance company management, festival production, grant-funded projects, and assorted professional services. Collection includes correspondence, printed material, and business and financial records created by Charles L. Reinhart and the employees of Charles Reinhart Management, Inc., 1956-1992.
ADF.003
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Patrons must sign the Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Provenance
The Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records were received by the American Dance Festival Archives as a transfer in 1998.
Historical Note
Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. (CRMI) was involved in dance company management, festival production, grant-funded projects, and assorted professional services. Companies managed included the Paul Taylor Dance Company, Meredith Monk/The House, the Glen Tetley Dance Company, the Don Redlich Dance Company, the Lucas Hoving Dance Company, and the Donald McKayle Dance Company, among others. Dance events produced in New York City included the City Center Spring Dance Festival (1969–1973), the dance seasons at the American National Theater and Academy (ANTA) and the City Center for Music and Drama (1968–1973), and the Dance Repertory Season at the Billy Rose Theatre (1969). Mr. Reinhart was the National Coordinator of the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Dance Touring Program from 1967 to 1978. He also developed the dance component of the NEA’s Artists-in-Schools Program (later the Artists-in-Education Program) and served as its National Coordinator from 1970 to 1981.
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, printed material, and business and financial records created by Charles L. Reinhart and the employees of Charles Reinhart Management, Inc., 1956-1992. Some personal papers of Charles L. Reinhart are also included.
Subject Headings
ANTA (Organization); Charles Reinhart Management, Inc.; Hoving, Lucas; McKayle, Donald, 1930-; Monk, Meredith; National Endowment for the Arts. Artists-in-Education Program; National Endowment for the Arts. Dance Program; Redlich, Don; Reinhart, Charles L., 1930-; Taylor, Paul, 1930-; Tetley, Glen; Choreographers -- United States; Modern dance -- United States
Contents of Collection
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - Fire Island, Paid and Unpaid Bills Blue House (Box 1)
  - Blue House, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Blue House (Box 1)
  - Divorce from Patricia M. Reinhart, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Gusta van der Wyck (Box 1)
  - Accident, Oct. 20, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Contracts Blue House (Box 1)
  - Bank of Babylon, 1966-1969 (Box 1)
  - Blue House (Box 1)
  - AIS Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - AIS Directory, Interested Companies and Teachers (not on the program), 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - AIS Applicants Review Panel Meeting, Sept. 17, 1974 (Box 1)
  - DMS/CO Applicants (Box 1)
  - AIS Announcement and Application for Cos. and DMT's who wish to participate, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Letters of Acceptance and Rejection, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Teacher Applications Calendar (by state) (Box 1)
  - AIS Applicants, Consultant Visits, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Copies of Consultant Reports, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Arlington Dance Theatre, 1974 (Box 1)
  - The Atlanta Ballet, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Ballet Hispanico of New York, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Boston Ballet, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Brockport Resident Dance Company, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Contemporary Dance System, New York, New York (Box 1)
  - First Chamber Dance Company, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Chuck Davis Dance Company, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Ballet, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Margalit Dance Theatre, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Mariano Parra Spanish Dance Company, 1974 (Box 1)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Phyllis Rose Dance Company, New York (Box 1)
  - Theatre Flamenco of San Francisco, 1974 (Box 1)
  - AIS/DC Applicants, Final Listing of Engagements Viewed, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Linda, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Berry, Kelly Marie, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Joan C., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Burd, Joyce, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Combest, Sandi, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Crabbe, Betsy, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Danish, Barbara, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Davis, Jaqueline, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Earl, William, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Evans, William, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Friedler, Sharon, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Guy, Kathyanne, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Halloran, Susan, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Handler, Darlene C., 1974 (Box 1)
  - Haynes, Kathleen Verity, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Hellman, Shiela, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Judith Jacobs, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Raymond, 1974 (Box 1)
  - King, Bruce, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Knox, Laura Toffel, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Lister, Merle, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Mason, Kathleen Criddle, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Mayer, Gregg, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Summer Workshop Receipts, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Accting. (Rm and Board Bill), 1976 (Box 2)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Expenses, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Expenses, Grant R60, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, 1976 (Box 2)
  - AIS R70-51-47N Cash Requests, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - AIS Grant Application and Budget Specifications, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - AIS R70-51-47N Grant Letter, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Copies of DMS and Travel Checks, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Grant 70-51-47N, AIS/DC, Summer Workshop Planning Meeting Expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Miscellaneous Expenses, 1977 (Box 2)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Preliminary Budget, Grant R-70-51-47N, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, A-D, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, E-K, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, L-S, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Summer Workshop Travel Reimbursement, T-Z, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Travel Reimbursement, Summer Workshop Check Copies, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Multiple Miscellaneous Forms (Box 2)
  - Outstanding Travel Reimbursements, Summer Workshop, 1977 (Box 2)
  - AIS Final Grant Report R80-51-47N, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - AIS/DC Endowment Grant R80-51-47N Cash Requests, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - AIS Dance Component Travel Reimbursement, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - AIS Senehan Grant to NEA, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - AIS Grant, Senehan Worksheets for Application, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - AIS/DC Grant R80-51-47N, Grant Letter, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - AIS Dance Component Workshop Expenses, R80-51-47N, 1978 (Box 2)
  - AIS Reimbursements Summer Workshop, Holding, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Planning Meeting, AIS Workshop Expenses, 27100 (Box 2)
  - Hawaii (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Idaho, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Indiana (Box 3)
  - Iowa (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Massachusetts (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Minnesota (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Nevada, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - New Jersey, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - New York (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - North Carolina (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - North Dakota, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Ohio, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Oregon, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Pennsylvania, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Tennessee, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Washington State (III), 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - AIS Directory Printing Costs, All Years (Box 3)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, AIE Travel Reimbursement Forms, Summer Workshops (A-L), 1981 (Box 3)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, AIE Travel Reimbursement Forms, Summer Workshops (M-Z), 1981 (Box 3)
  - AIS Endowment Grant Applications (Box 3)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Housing, Guest Registration Forms, Half-Price Ticket Vouchers, Summer Workshop, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Housing, Guest Registration Forms, Summer Workshop, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Ririe-Woodbury Point System (Box 4)
  - AIS/ADF Project (Box 4)
  - ADF Courses Duke Approved (Box 4)
  - Smithsonian/ADF (Box 4)
  - ADF, Selma Jeanne Cohen (Box 4)
  - ADF, The Arts Environment (Box 4)
  - Ohio Keynote Speech (Box 4)
  - Philadelphia (Box 4)
  - AIS Speeches (Box 4)
  - AIS/Dance Component Bibliographies (Box 4)
  - Dance in the Public Schools: Developing Professional Standards, Certification, and Curricula, Marquette Public Schools (Box 4)
  - The National Committee, Arts for the Handicapped (Box 4)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Documentation of Work with Handicapped (Box 4)
  - Curriculum Development Materials (Box 4)
  - Department of Defense AIS Programs, JanaLee Sponberg (Box 4)
  - Arts Endowment Correspondence, July 1, 1980 (Box 4)
  - National Endowment For The Arts Draft, Future of AIS Program (Box 4)
  - NEA AIS Components Other Than Dance (Box 4)
  - Mtg with Joe Prinee, Aug. 22, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Shirlie Ririe, History of AIS Dance (Box 4)
  - AIS Review Process, Announcement of Endowment Deadline, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - NEA AIS Advisory Panel Meeting, May 19, 20, 21, 1980 (Box 4)
  - National Endowment For The Arts and National Council On The Arts, Annual Report, the arts, 1969 (Box 4)
  - National Council on the Arts and National Endowment for the Arts, Report of the Task Force on the Education, Training and Development of Professional Artists and Art Educators, Dec. 1978 (Box 4)
  - AIE Workshop, Staff Assignments, Part-Time Staff and Work Force, 1981 (Box 4)
  - NEA CA 80-4 Contract Release Forms (Box 4)
  - Dancing In The Schools: The National Endowment for the Arts; Artists-in-Schools/Dance Component (Box 4)
  - AIS Handbook Grant #R70-51-95N, Grant Letter/Application (Box 4)
  - Senehan (Box 4)
  - AIS General Planning Strategy and Calendar (Box 4)
  - AIS Dance Component Grant 02-5150-072 Grant Letter and Forms, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Calendar/Paymt. Schedule (orig), Requests for DMS Fees/Travel Sheet (orig), Last Grant (Box 4)
  - AIE Workshop Expenses, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Graduate AIS Workshop (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, National Endowment For The Arts, Dec. 14, 1981 (Box 4)
  - AIS Grant, Last One, Budget, 1981 (Box 4)
  - NEA Requirements for "Professional Dance Companies" (Box 4)
  - U.S. Department of Education General Information (Box 4)
  - Evaluation Tools for AIS (Box 4)
  - AIS Program Right/Left Brain Theory Materials (Box 4)
  - Education Publications (Box 4)
  - Commerce Dept. (Box 4)
  - AIS/Dance Component Graduate Workshop (Box 4)
  - AIS FYI Workshop Issue (not originals), June 1979 (Box 5)
  - FYI, 1979 (Box 5)
  - FYI Special Workshop Edition, June 1979 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Info/Ideas To be Included, Jan. 1980 (Box 5)
  - FYI, June 1980 (Box 5)
  - FYI, 1980 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Sept. 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Lists of Films/Slides/Videotapes, etc., Dec. 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Feb. 1979 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Apr. 1979 (Box 5)
  - FYI, May 1979 (Box 5)
  - AIS/Dance Component, FYI, Feb. 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Mar. 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Apr. 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Mar. 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, June 1978 (Box 5)
  - FYI, June 1977 (Box 5)
  - FYI Rejects (Box 5)
  - FYI, Jan. 1977 (Box 5)
  - FYI Originals, Dec. 1977 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Apr. 1977 (Box 5)
  - FYI, May 1977 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Feb. 1976 (Box 5)
  - FYI, June 1976 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Sept. 1976 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Nov. 1976 (Box 5)
  - FYI Originals, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - FYI Originals, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - FYI Originals, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Jan. 1975 (Box 5)
  - FYI, Mar. 1975 (Box 5)
  - FYI, May 1975 (Box 5)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, FYI Compendium, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, FYI Compendium, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, FYI Compendium, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, FYI Compendium, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, FYI Compendium, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, FYI Compendium, 1980 (Box 5)
  - DMS and DC Employment Stat. (Box 6)
  - Calender Changes, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
  - AIS/DC Calendars, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Assistants (DMS), 1980-1981 (Box 6)
  - AIS Calendars, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Artists Advisory Committee, Educators/State Art, Age 4, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
  - Bhaskar (Box 6)
  - Virginia Tanner (contains photographic materials) (Box 6)
  - AIS Steering Committee, Evaluation of AIS Programs, 1980 (Box 6)
  - AIS Planning: MTG with C. Davis/Discussion with J. Woodbury (Box 6)
  - Norman Worrell Study about National Coordinators (Box 6)
  - AIS/DC Kudos (Box 6)
  - National Coordinators for AIS, Miscellaneous Information (Box 6)
  - Artists Advisory Committee AIS (Box 6)
  - AIS Artists Advisory Committee Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Forms from Susan Sachs Re: Evaluation of Program (Box 6)
  - Artists Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Artists Advisory Committee Funding Requests (Box 6)
  - AIS Artists Advisory Committee Mailing Re Co. Selection for Workshop (Box 6)
  - Role of National Coordinator: Mtg of Natl Coor., Oct. 26, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Crystal Samuels (Box 6)
  - Marryl Dee Cahill, Traveling to AIS Sites (Box 6)
  - AIS Dance Component, Evaluating Effectiveness of AIS Dance Programs (Box 6)
  - AIS Guidelines, Letters from School/SAA/Artists (Box 6)
  - Partnership, AIS, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Support for 2 WKS of Dance Co, AIS /Dance Component Guidelines (Box 6)
  - Administration, Finance, ADF; CRMI, Auto Maintenance; Reimbursement, Lee Woodbury (ADF Finance Coordinator), 1979 (Box 6)
  - Administration, Finance, CRMI; ADF, Dues and Subscriptions 2.1, Charles Reinhart, 1974-1980 (Box 6)
  - Administration, Finance CRMI (account 422000); ADF and AIS, Reimbursement, Dance Classes 8.1, 1979-1981 (Box 6)
  - Administration, Finance CRMI, Reimbursement, Dance Performance Tickets 8.3, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Administration, Finance, ADF (accts 430004, 380004) Entertainment and Gifts 8.2, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - Meredith Monk, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Tetley, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Tetley, 1967-1978 (Box 7)
  - Tetley (Box 7)
  - Tetley Contracts, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - 1110-1114 (Box 7)
  - Rent and Wage and Tax Escalation, Cross and Brown Inc., Feb. 1978 (Box 7)
  - CRMI Leases 1, Rent History (Box 7)
  - John Perras (Box 7)
  - Isham (Insurance) Agency and Merchants Insurance Information (Box 7)
  - The Insurance House of Deer Park, Cancelling of Insurance Policies (Box 7)
  - CRMI Insurance (Box 7)
  - CRMI Tetley, Taylor, and Redlich Tour Sched., 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence Re: Pension/Profit Emp. Des. Comp. Systems (Box 7)
  - Correspondence Re: Wertheim (Box 7)
  - CRMI Wertheim Pension (Box 7)
  - Wertheim and Co., Profit Sharing Portfolio Information (Box 7)
  - Wertheim and Co., CRMI Portfolio Info (Box 7)
  - Taxes, Pension, Profit Sharing Plan (Box 7)
  - ADF: Employee Pension Plan (Box 7)
  - Guardian Policies (Box 7)
  - CR, Life Insurance, Guardian (Box 7)
  - Employee Compensation/Dan Mazzola Correspondence (Box 7)
  - Pension/Profit Sharing (Box 7)
  - Plan Description (Box 7)
  - History (Box 7)
  - Pension, Profit Sharing (Box 7)
  - Group Annuity Contracts (Box 7)
  - Wertheim Correspondence, Paul Schupf Correspondence (Box 7)
  - N.C. Insurance Company(s) Survey, July 1983 (Box 7)
  - SSR Medical Bills and Insurance Claims, PRC, 1979 (Box 7)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General (see Subcategories), 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Evaluations, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Summer Workshop, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General (see Subcategories), 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General (see Subcategories), 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Synthesis of Workshop Evaluations, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Housing, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Housing, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Memos that went out re:workshop, 1974 (Box 8)
  - AIS Workshop, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, Supplementary Handouts/Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS Workshop, Memos/Agenda/Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, Packet Material Originals and Handouts, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, Evaluation Forms Returned, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, CRMI Pre-Planning MTG, Mar. 31, 1975 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Planning Session, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS Workshop Packet, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, CRMI Staff Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, All Memos File, Original Copies, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Workshop/MTG, Room Information Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS.DC Summer Workshop MTG, Final Agenda, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, Group Leaders, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Agenda, Drafts and Suggestions, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/MTG, Letters of Appreciation, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - AIS Workshop Planning Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Agenda, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Invitations/Mailing List, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Original Memos, AIS Workshop, Memos Sent Prior To and Following Up Workshop, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Carol's Notes SW, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Registration Memo, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Xeroxes of Memos Sent Prior To and Following Workshop, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Complete Kit, 1979 (Box 9)
  - S. Dilley Workshop Kit, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Kit, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Speakers (includes Expectations Session), 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Notes on Kit Materials, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Technique and Workshop Classes, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Staff Assignments and Responsibilities, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Spaces for Sessions, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Total Attendance Participants Composition of Workshop, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Artists Booked, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Group Leaders, Selection and Confirmation, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Notes: Lili Conversations, June 21, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Orientation, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Artist Attendance Exceptions, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop NEA AIS Advisory Panel and other VIP's, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Ririe, Woodbury C.O. Performance, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Announcements and Preparation for Discussion Sessions, 1979 (Box 9)
  - VIPS, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Thank You Notes, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Suggestions for Next Year, Misc, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Drafts of Agenda and Final Changes on Final Agenda, Planning Agenda, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Independent Screenings, SW, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Memos Sent Out Re: Workshop, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Summer Workshop Memos, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Kit Originals and Other Handouts, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - General Conference Information (Box 9)
  - Registration Exceptions, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Summer Workshop Kit Materials, 1979 (Box 9)
  - ADF Organizational Chart (Box 9)
  - Full Workshop Agenda (Box 9)
  - Things to Do in Durham (Box 9)
  - Map of Duke University, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Workshop Correspondence (Box 9)
  - Participants List (Box 9)
  - Press Release (Box 9)
  - Evaluation Form, AIS/DC Workshop (Box 9)
  - Workshop Evaluations, Evaluation Compilation, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS/ DC Workshop Planning Meeting, Memos to Committee, 1979 (Box 9)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, ADF Press Release Kit for AIS VIP's, 1978 (Box 9)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Equipment, 1978 (Box 9)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Xeroxes of Memos, 1978 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop Kit Materials, 1978 (Box 9)
  - AIS Workshop, Equipment, Space, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Summer Workshop Planning Meeting, 1978 (Box 9)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Kit Originals, 1978 (Box 9)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Artists Selections, Wkshps/Tech. and Speakers, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Photographs and Contact Sheets, Arthur Hall's Afro-American Dance Ensemble Residency, Hart Junior High School, Philadelphia, PA, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Reports on Residency of Arthur Hall's Afro-American Dance Ensemble, Hart Junior High School, Philadelphia, PA, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Printed Materials Related to Arthur Hall's Afro-American Dance Ensemble's Residency, Hart Junior High School, Philadelphia, PA, 1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS State Arts Agency Preferences, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - ESAA Info, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - USOE Proposal given to Ed Programs on Phone, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - USOE, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Manpower Development and Training Act, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS Dance Movement Teacher Assistants, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Dance Movement Teacher Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS/DC Teacher and Asst Contracts Originals, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Assistant Dance Movement Teacher Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Assistant Dance Movement Teacher Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS Mov't Teacher Statement, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS Company Statement, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - AIS Calendar and Final Report Calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - State Reports to NEA, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Alaska, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Delaware, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - D.C., 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - Hawaii, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Idaho, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Illinois, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Iowa, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Maine, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Maryland (III), 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - Massachusetts, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - DMS Dance Co. Applicants, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - Magic Movers (Box 11)
  - Morca, Flamenco in Concert (Box 11)
  - One Plus One, Inc. (Box 11)
  - Sounds In Motion, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - AIS/DC Application Requests, Directory and Supplement, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Review Process For Directory, Old Reports on Previous Applicants, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Applications For DMS and DC For Directory, Aug. 20, 1979 (Box 11)
  - National Endowment For The Arts, Memorandum, Nov. 16, 1979 (Box 11)
  - 1981-1982 Directory Review Panel Mtg., Meeting I, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - Directory Review Process, Mar. 17, 1980 (Box 11)
  - AIS Review Panel II Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - AIS/DC Application Requests (Box 11)
  - Application Suggestions, DMS and Dance Co., NEA/AIS Dance Comp. (Box 11)
  - Extra Letters of Rec (Box 11)
  - Panel Meeting Costs, AIS, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - AIS Review Process, Directory, Post-Review Responses and Complaints, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - AIS Review Process, Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - AIS Review Process, On Site Reviews for Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Consultants (Box 11)
  - Review Policy (Box 11)
  - Review Consultants Report Procedure (Box 11)
  - Lists of Applicants, All Years (Box 11)
  - To Help Organize Review Files (Box 11)
  - Review Consultants Memos et al. (Box 11)
  - Presently Participating DMS and DC Review, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - ReReview (Box 11)
  - ReReview (Box 11)
  - Dance Cos. and Dance MVT. Spec. Who Haven't Participated in Three Years, ReReview (Box 11)
  - ReReview Reports, 1978 (Box 11)
  - M. Anthony Dance Co. (Box 11)
  - Bruce King (Box 11)
  - Kelly-Marie Berry (Box 11)
  - Blanche Felsher (Box 11)
  - California, Mary McKinney Complaint Against CAC (Box 11)
  - Artists' Meeting, re: Review and Hauser, Jan. 13, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Misc. Complaints, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Erik Whitmyre (Box 11)
  - Oumansky (Box 11)
  - Review of Bhaskar, 1977 (Box 11)